FROM ME TO YOU
On the days I don't go to school, I start
with feeding some rice to the little birds
outside.
After that, I go for a jog.
Combustible trash.
Recyclable trash.
COMBUSTIBLE TRASH
RECYCLABLE TRASH
And then I go home and shower.
Usually, there's more. I'd clean and
eat breakfast to complete my routine, but
today...
Chizu and Ayane are coming
over to hang out with me.
DAY OFF
Ohhh! That's right, huh! You have some
friends coming over today, don't you?
- They're here! What do I do?!
- I'll get the door for ya.
Sawako's dad, right?
- Delinquent...
- You look just like her!
- Don't be rude! Say hi!
- H- Hi there.
D- Does that mean
you're Sawako's... friends?
This one seems like a nice young
lady. Little heavy on the makeup, but...
Nice to meet you.
We're classmates. I'm Yano.
How many piercings does she have?
Y-You're really my daughter's friends?
Chizu! Ayane!
Hi. Welcome! I'm making a cake for us!
You mean from scratch?!
Really? Uhh... we had the same thought.
A cake! Oh, that's too bad... I should
have thought ahead and made something
- salty... I'm so sorry.
- Nah. Homemade's way
tastier than storebought.
- I'll take any slice I can get!
- There are consequences to that, ya know.
Oh! My... What's this? No need to stand in
front of the door! Please come in and make
- yourselves at home!
- This is my mom. And that is my dad.
Nice to meet ya!
We brought this, but since Sawako
already made one, would you like it?
My goodness! Thank you very much, girls!
This is Ayane Yano and
that's Chizuru Yoshida.
Thanks for taking care of Sawako.
Yeah, they really do take good care of me
Well, Sawako's always
looking after us too...
This girl? Sawako
helped her pass her exam.
- Jeez, Yano-chin, that's so embarrassing!
- It's the truth though.
Woah. Your room's more
colorful than I expected.
Well, I figured it's private, so
no one would mind it not suiting me.
Oh, you...
You're totally overthinking.
Oh, what's this?! Ya got a
couple pictures up here!
I looked for pictures from our field
trip, and I was able to find some with the
- three of us together...
- These aren't just a ghost
that was caught on camera?
These aren't just a ghost
Then this is perfect.
Here! It's a little gift.
SAWAKO
Wow!
- These are from the after-party.
- They're nice shots, right?
Amazing! You can tell I'm a living human
being in them! We're so close together!
You guys...
You should look at all of them.
Wh- When did I put him in
such an awkward situation?!
Yano-chin took it in secret.
Pretty nice, huh? Like you're a couple.
I must've been so heavy.
He might be a wimp, but a man's still
gotta be able to support a woman at least.
- Ya know?
- Heeey! That's mean!
That's the one where
Kazehaya noticed I was there.
In a matter of seconds, my
treasures have multiplied!
Thank you guys.
But you shouldn't be
satisfied with just a few pictures.
You should tell him how you're feeling.
- Tell who? Tell him what?
- Kazehaya, your love.
Love?!
I'm in love with you.
You don't say?
But for what purpose?
For the two of you to
start dating, obviously!
No way. Impossible.
- But it is possible...
- Okay. How do I put this? The way things
stand right now, I'm already overwhelmed.
Anything more than this... I
can't even imagine it, so...
You say that now, but what if
Kazehaya gets taken by someone else, huh?
I don't think that I could support them...
At the very least I wouldn't celebrate it...
M- My bad, I shouldn't have said that!
I'm sorry! But I get it. Just liking him
doesn't mean you're ready to
skip to dating or anything, right?
- I feel bad for the guy...
- What are these?
Ah! I rented those for us yesterday.
- You wanna watch?
- Ooh! That sounds nice!
Get me out of here!
Ryu!
- Pedro...
- Look how happy he is. I can
- tell you really love animals.
- He's cute.
I wonder who that could be.
PIN
090-1XXX-XXXX
- What's up?
- It's Pin. It stopped
I have 14 missed calls?!
And they're all from him?!
- You gonna answer?
- Nah. It's actually been ringing for a
while now, but I left it alone 'cause it's
a pain to pick up.
PIN
090-1XXX-XXXX
- What do you--
- The hell have you been
- doing this whole time?!
- It's none of your
business, why do you care?!
You... bring Kuronuma over right
away. Got it? Good. And make it snappy.
Counting on you... Can't stop shaking...
Actually... I ran into her
while I was out last night.
Good evening. Are you here to do
some research as well, Mr. Arai?
R-18
EROTIC SPECIAL
Uh-huh! That's what this is!
Research? On what? Ghost photos?
Those are for adults, right?
She saw right through me.
Films on social issues... Documentaries...
He is a grown-up. Totally makes sense.
D- Do you-?
- What is it? What do you see behind me?
- Huh... He sounds a bit congested.
Come on... Why are you staring?
Um... Mr. Arai... When you get home, make
sure to wash your hands, and you should
- also rinse your mouth with salt water.
- Huh? Please. You can
never be too careful.
Why does she want me to purify myself?!
But after all that, I went home and
completely forgot about her warning.
Woo-hoo!
- That's everything.
- So, uh...
All I got from that was
how he rented dirty videos.
Please, kid... I'm counting on you.
What did he say?
I still don't really know,
but he did sound pretty weak.
Huh.
And he said to bring Kuronuma there.
Ah, now that you mention it, Chizuru
told me she was going to her house today.
I could bring Maru...
Will Sawako end up a delinquent?
Is she okay?
Oh! My! Look at this!
Five different cakes!
They were thoughtful enough to bring two
extra portions for us from the beginning.
How sweet of them!
- Thank you for the cake!
- Oh, you didn't need to bother.
Well, they started watching some scary
movies in the room. It's an excuse to slip
- out.
- Oh just leave them there sweetheart.
It's fine, let me wash
them. Can I use this?
I'm super good at washing dishes!
Look, quick and sparkling clean!
- Oh, you're right.
- Ya see?
Thank you, dear. You
didn't need to do all that.
It's fine! I'm proud of this skill!
Sawako has the same
eyebrows, eyes, and nose as her dad.
But she got her face shape and
lips from her mom. Warms my heart.
How rare. See ya!
Kazehaya? What's up?
Both of them are actually
very nice girls, aren't they?
Uh-huh!
Huh? Yeah, sure, we'll go.
Uh-huh. What? That's creepy!
You're right, it's super weird. I'm
honestly a little spooked. But at least I
- have Maru with me!
- Maru?
Kazehaya?
Yeah.
Kuronuma?
Pin says he's not feeling too well, and
he wanted to ask you for advice, so... I
- thought we could all go to his place.
- I knew it.
It makes sense. Once you have a stuffy
nose, rinsing your mouth's pointless.
Be right there!
That's good.
I'm sure Maru wants to see you too.
Yeah.
Was that it?
What do you mean?
You didn't say, "I wanna
see you too," or anything.
I thought... you'd be the
type to say that is all
Well, I'm not!
Today... is a great day.
Not only do I have my friends
over, I get to see Kazehaya too.
Yo, finally.
I'm... done for.
- This place is disgusting.
Okay. Tell me. How are
things looking, doc?
Awful. Let's put these
covers on you for starters.
A cold.
- It's a cold.
- It's literally just a cold.
For now, I kinda... brought
you a variety of things.
Exorcism tools?
- I'll do it!
- And also this... I can feed him!
This too...
And...
Oh, come on. Why am I taking
care of Pin like we're dating?
What a caretaker!
Hey, you think I'm okay?
- You think this room's okay?
- The heck are you even growling at, Pedro?
Just last night, I heard this
high-pitched screech, like something was
scratching.
The fever's so bad, his ears are
ringing! Don't worry. Please just relax
and get some sleep.
This room... may take a little work, but
I'll be sure to give it a proper cleaning
while you rest. It's fine. I'm
actually very good at this sort of thing.
Warding off evil spirits?
Cleaning... is fun.
Hey, want me to tell you a
bedtime story to lull you to sleep?
Huh? Okay. Why not.
Then here's one I just picked up
recently. It's a true story, and it
actually happened in this very
neighborhood. It all started at this
single guy's apartment, he would
hear a knock on his door every night.
But when he swung the door open, there was
never anyone standing on the other side.
And that's because, in reality,
all along, at that very apartment...
Despite getting all freaked
out, he's sleeping like a baby.
It's a miniature Kazehaya!
That's my fault! I'm so
sorry. I violated your privacy...
No! it's just it's embarrassing!
In that one... I was just
frustrated that we lost the game.
And Pin was making fun of me for crying.
Just one more look?
No! You can't! Oh! You haven't
gotten to pet Maru yet, right?
It's just I'd feel bad if I
got between him and Sanada!
- W-What about now then?
- S-Sure!
- Why don't they just get together already?
Sooo cuuuute!
He's out cold, huh?
Mmhm, sure is.
- I feel lighter.
- The medicine must've kicked in.
- Even the air feels different now!
- Because we ventilated the room.
Because we ventilated the room.
You're amazing! Next time I'm
possessed, I'll count on you!
What? You guys're
still loafing around here?
- Wha...
We're leavin' you for dead next time!
- T- take care.
- Unbelievable. Well
- that was a total waste.
- Hey, I know there's not much I can do to
repay you, but if you need advice, come
ask me.
Just sayin' if it's about Shota or Ryu, I
know it all. Wanna learn their weaknesses?
I got you.
That jerk better not be
telling her anything about me.
And Shota...
- I-Is that true?
- Completely! If you wanna thank him,
that's the way. He'll be thrilled!
He'd be thrilled?
But, man, I feel light as a feather,
this is the beeeest! What, did they forget
something?
Sawako, your cake was so freakin' yummy!
Well, things didn't quite go
as planned, But we'll try again!
Yes please! Come again!
You know... after being together pretty
much all day, leaving's kinda hard.
The more time we spend with one
another, it becomes harder and harder to
say goodbye.
'Kay. I'll be going this way.
See you guys. Get back safe.
Well aren't you gonna walk her home?
Yeah, that's right! It's
dangerous when it's this dark out!
It's fine! I-I'll make sure not to
scare anyone on the way back. I'll be
- extra careful!
- I'll go.
Okay?
But I...
No? If you don't want me to...
It's not that I don't.
If Shota's going, then I'll go.
- Idiot! You're coming with us.
- Pedro...
- See ya!
- Good night!
- Give our regards to your mom and dad!
- I- I will!
Let's go.
Of course I want this.
There's no way I wouldn't.
- The days are starting to get short.
- Yeah...
I'm happy.
Maybe even too happy... to the point where
I want to thank you so much, but I just
can't find the words.
Or even look you in the eyes.
- Whoa!
- You! I-I Uuuuh!
- Uh- so- just now was that~ Huh?!
Um, Mr. Arai said that if I wanted to
thank you, I should grab you, then close
- my eyes and count all the way up to five.
- That rat bastard...
Be careful, kay?
It's just, if you try that again,
I don't know how I might react.
I really don't know what I'd do.
The more... the more I hear his voice.
Spend time with him...
Catch glimpses of his face...
I was right... the harder
it becomes to say goodbye.
- Just for a little, don't look at me 'kay?
- Okay...
One day... will I want to tell him
the way I was feeling... on this night?
Winter is coming.
The footsteps of hope.
Next time: "Chizuru's Love"